[
  {
      "level": 1,
      "questionId": "#qs01",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "To initiate the supercomputer, please provide the access key. In the name of my love, a code conceals, Convert each letter, the sum reveals.",
      "correctAnswer": "107",
      "questionAssets": []
  },
  {
      "level": 2,
      "questionId": "#qs02",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "The supercomputer shows Dtzw sjcy xytu nx f uqfsjy YTN733g. Jsyjw inxyfshj ns qnlmy djfwx yt htsynszj.",
      "correctAnswer": 245.5,
      "questionAssets": []
  },
  {
      "level": 3,
      "questionId": "#qs03",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "Already aware, where to head next. Your spaceship lifted off from earth and started moving towards the planet. Traveling through space your spaceship encounters various anomalies. It Ascends 116 units. Then, it Speeds up by 111m/s. Then it Coasts for 107 units. Then it Ingresses for 101 minutes. Then it moves with an Impulse of 110 N/m^2.",
      "correctAnswer": "token",
      "questionAssets": []
  },
  {
      "level": 4,
      "questionId": "#qs04",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "Your journey continues. In your spaceship certain frequencies are detected when you connect with the frequency you get something. In realms of hex where digits align, Unravel the puzzle, where dimensions entwine. A secret lies in the code so grand, Clue's product, in hex, reveals its command.",
      "correctAnswer": "840C04",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "image",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  },
  {
      "level": 5,
      "questionId": "#qs05",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "Now you all again started moving towards the planet. In the path a solar storm hit the spaceship the spaceship was lost in the solar vortex. In pictures I hide, unseen by the eye, At the text's end, the answer does lie.",
      "correctAnswer": "escape",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "image",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  },
  {
      "level": 6,
      "questionId": "#qs06",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "Your satellite breaks free from the solar storm, but you lose your trajectory and drift towards a new planet. Upon crashing, consciousness begins to slip away. When awareness returns, you find yourselves facing unfamiliar extraterrestrial beings. None of you can comprehend or communicate with them; their language remains a mystery. They confine you to their jail, where you marvel at their advanced technology. Glancing at the cell walls, you notice a picture pasted there.",
      "correctAnswer": "Instagram",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "image",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  },
  {
      "level": 7,
      "questionId": "#qs07",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "your friend receives signal on his wrist band it states aHR0cHM6Ly90b29scy5rbm93bGVkZ2V3YWxscy5jb20vb25saW5lLXNlY3JldC1tZXNzYWdlLWVuY29kZXItZGVjb2Rlcj9taT1iM2xETkM5WlpXdE9XR0pXZDNnMVRXUjBOaXRNWnowOU9qcVJVaFRuRDZ5ZjZleTdiaHdVZSUyQlli In the code's inception, Base64 sets the scene, Unlock the gate with answers, from replies that've been.",
      "correctAnswer": "leave",
      "questionAssets": []
  },
  {
      "level": 8,
      "questionId": "#qs08",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "As you gather, realizing escape is your only option, you hastily board the spaceship, resuming your journey. Lost and directionless, uncertainty clouds your path. Suddenly, an image emerges, revealingâ€¦ In a sequence I align, a path to unveil, Connect me in order, a form to prevail. From point to point, a shape takes flight, Arrange me right, reveal what's in sight.",
      "correctAnswer": "Umbrella",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "image",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  },
  {
      "level": 9,
      "questionId": "#qs09",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "After landing on the planet you all started looking around on the new planet. You found a dome shaped ecosystem. You get close to it and see a ball. A 3d holographic character comes out. It says something but you all couldn't hear but one of your friends records his voice.",
      "correctAnswer": "AlmostThere",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "audio",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  },
  {
      "level": 10,
      "questionId": "#qs10",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "Upon opening the dome, you see your father waiting for you. Tears roll down your eyes, and happiness fills your father's gaze. There are many questions you want to ask him. You inquire, \"What is happening?\" and inquire about the alien civilization that aided you. Your father explains that Earth was devastated by an asteroid collision. He maintained contact with scientists from the alien planet who rescued him. They informed him about the collision, and somehow he managed to escape Earth and come to this planet. He further reveals that this planet is very close to a black hole, where time moves slowly, which is why he is still alive. You all begin working on how to rehabilitate Earth by exploring a parallel universe. However, one day, everything stops working, and errors abound. I'm not always what I seem to portray, Explore beyond the surface, where truths disguise.",
      "correctAnswer": "debugged",
      "questionAssets": []
  },
  {
      "level": 11,
      "questionId": "#qs11",
      "questionTitle": "",
      "questionBody": "After that one day while working you all detect some frequencies with a message written: Echoes of my melody, silent in the air, Decode my essence, convert sound to visual glare. 01000001 01110101 01100100 01100001 01100011 01101001 01110100 01111001 00001010",
      "correctAnswer": "HubbleTelescope",
      "questionAssets": [
          {
              "type": "audio",
              "url": "https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/12Nty3i31cziJw2TWx4Hn3gmt1-fxML87"
          }
      ]
  }
]
